What is the name of the drunkard?
dịu nào danh cho người say đáng cay đầu
What is the bitterness? Vuong Bao, from his heart full of love, his head is
nào hay sót Vương bao từ lòng chẫn tình
white, he sees that the world is in his place, who knows?  I
thay biết ai đâu dãi bày dọ sâu còn mãi
don&#39;t bother to marry
m ngưng bay gió kia chẳng buồn lấy la
a flower and play far away from the scene. After the green day, I have to be
hoa chơi xa cảnh sau ngày xanh đã phải
with a new person. I&#39;m happy with someone who still has the King for
bên mới em vui cùng ai có vẫn Vương cho
me. Even if life is absent from me, my heart
này dù đời vắng bóng sáng em CN tim
won&#39;t be able to face
không đối
[music]
[âm nhạc]
or the way we know each other, we won&#39;t be together.
hay đường quen ta không trung lối sẽ trở
Being far away means we&#39;ve
nên xa là ci từng thế hẹn Không Chung
been together for a long time. If we&#39;re not together, we&#39;ll forget it. But the day you
Đôi sẽ quên thôi mà ngày em bước đi ngăn
walk away, it&#39;s because of the ice season.  Where is the
so vì mùa băng x Mình Anh đi lang thang
wind taking the boat to the other side? It&#39;s a desolate,
ngang vui tình duyên khác gió đưa thuyền
melancholy port. We&#39;re
về đâu Bến hoang vắng u sầu định mnh ta
separated from each other, holding on to so many regrets. Which goat mountain is
xa dời nhau ôm bao tiếc Núi dêu nào dành
for the drunkard?
cho người say cng C đâu nào hay Sát
Where&#39;s the good place? The King&#39;s heart is full of heartbreak and first love. I don&#39;t
Vương bao từ lòng trẫn tình đầu chẳng
see if it&#39;s the cause.  Time changes, I don&#39;t know who&#39;s there, the deep and
thấy có phải nhân gian đổi thay biết ai
deep still remain forever, the
đâu dãi bày dọ sâu còn mãi chất chưa nỗi
pain I ask, the sky is sad, I
đau con hoi trời buồn Ngà m ngưng bay
don&#39;t even want to let the wind fly, I don&#39;t even bother to be a flower and play far
gió kia chẳng buồn lấy la hoa chơi xa
away, after the green day, I have to be with a new person, I&#39;m
cảnh sau ngày xanh đã phải bên mới em
happy with someone who is still King of this place
vui cùng ai có vẫn Vương Chốn Này
Even though life is absent from my morning sun, my heart can&#39;t
dù đời vắng bóng sáng em CN tim không
face
đối
[music]
[âm nhạc]
or my hand has not forgotten the warmth of my kiss. Picking
hay bàn tay chưa quên hơi ấm chiếc hôn
up people, quickly moving across,
vẫn chưa Nhặt m người vội vng mau sang
happy, different love, where will the wind take the boat?
ngang vui tình duyên khác gió đưa thuyền
Desolate harbor.  I&#39;m so sad that we&#39;re
về đâu Bến hoang vắng u sầu định mình ta
far away from each other, holding on to all the regrets and tenderness
xa dời nhau ôm bao tiếc nuôi dịu nào
for those who are drunk and bitter. Where&#39;s the
dành cho người sayy đáng cay đâu nào hay
little thing that&#39;s missing? The heart of our first love, I
sót Vương bao Tơ Lòng trận tình đầu
can&#39;t see it. Is it the world? Thy
chẳng thấy có phải nhân gian đội Thy
knows who? The depth of her womb is still there
biết ai đâu dái bà dọ sâu còn mãi chất
forever. The sadness.  The pain is still there, Hoa is sad, a thousand
chưa Nỗi đau còn Hoà chời buồn một ngàn
planes stopped flying on that death anniversary, I don&#39;t bother to take la
máy ngừng bay giỗ kia chẳng buồn lấy la
flowers, not far away, the scene after the green day is less exposed to the
hoa chưa xa cảnh sau ngày xanh đỡ phơi
new side, I&#39;m happy with anyone, no one is attached to
bên mới em vui cùng ai có vấ vương chốn
this place, even though life is empty and bright, my heart is
này dù đời phắng bóng sáng em con tim
not gentle or
không đối
gentle.  For drunk people who are C,
hay dịu nào dành cho người say đang C
there is no place to miss. Phuong always guides love from his heart,
đâu nào hay sót Phương bao từ lòng dẫn
but he doesn&#39;t see if it&#39;s the world that&#39;s
tình đâu chẳng thấy có phải nhân gian
replaced. Who knows? Where can he confide that the deep feeling is still
đội thay biết ai đâu giãi bày dọ sâu còn
good? The pain still asks God, sadly, he
mãi chất chưa Nỗi đau còn hỏi trời buồn
hangs up, the other number doesn&#39;t bother to take it.
ngan máy ngng máy số kia chẳng buồn lấy
After the green day, I had to be with a
la hoa chơi xa cnh sau ngày xanh đã phải
new person. I&#39;m happy with everyone. I&#39;m still in
bên mới em vui cùng ai có vẫn Vương chỗn
this place. Even though life is absent, my heart
này dù đời vắng bóng sáng em con tim
can&#39;t
không đôi
see
thấy
[music] [
[âm nhạc]
Applause] [
[Vỗ tay]
Happy days with you don&#39;t last long.
ngày vui bên em chắng được bao lâu đàn
Night after night you
đêm em
cry with all your sorrows.
khóc theo những muôn sầu người con gái
When a girl loves someone with all her heart, she can&#39;t
khi yêu một ai hết lòng là chẳng phân
decide what&#39;s right. They
định được chuyện đúng
only tease you for a few
xi người ta chỉ trêu đùa em vài
days and then they chase you away.
hôm rồi người bó em chạy theo những
Quick flower
nhanh hoa
poetry I know that because V is heavy-hearted V that person
thơ em biết mà do V nặng lòng V người ấy
truly loves me, do you know
làm tôn thương anh thật lòng em biết
how similar they are to you Why does
không Người ta giống với em thế nào Sao
your scent have to be the color I feel like I want to feel
hương sắc em phải màu anh thấy muốn
sad shining on your melancholy eyes when the
phiền nặng chiếu trên đôi mắt em u sầu
happy day comes  I&#39;ve been by your side so many times,
ngày vui đến bên em bao lần ngày buồn
uninvited and sad, why do you always come so quickly, flowers and cheers,
không mời sao cứ đến một nhanh hoa hô
life screams and roars, look
những đời reo lên bao rống nhìn lại phía
behind you, you&#39;re not alone, baby,
sau lưng em này em không một mình đâu em
stop crying and cry for
à Thôi đí đi đừng khóc nữa nước mắt cho
those who deceived others.  If it&#39;s just for the night,
kẻ rồii lừa người ta đã Khuê đêm thôi
just let it go until it&#39;s
thì hãy buông đến cho nhẹ lòng thánh
a girl&#39;s holy spring,
xuân của người con gái ngăn lắm em biết
you know, baby, don&#39;t cry, think about it,
Em ơi đừng khóc nhé hãy nghĩ suy đi
but when you&#39;re with me, when you
mà khi đ có anh khi
know they&#39;re just teasing you, he
biết người ta chỉ trêu đùa em ngài
shouts and then your father runs away.  Following the
hô rồi người Bố em chạy theo những nhanh
fragrant flowers you know, why are you so close? My heart is heavy because that
hoa thơm em biết mà sao gần Nặng Lòng vì
person really hurts me, do you
người ấy làm tốn thương anh thật lòng em
know? How similar is that person to you?
biết không Người ta giống với em thế nào
Why does your scent have to be the same color? I see all the
Sao hương sắc em phải màu anh thấy muôn
heavy troubles shining on your melancholy eyes these
phiền nặng chiếu trên đôi mắt em u sầu
days.  Happiness comes to you many times, sad days are
ngày vui đến bên em bao lần ngày buồn
not good, flowers always come quickly,
không hời sa cứ đến một nhanh hoa hô
life screams loudly, look back at your
những đời reo lên bao rộ nhìn lại phía s
back, you are not alone,
lưng em này em không một mình đâu em à
stop crying, tears for
Thôi đín đi đừng khóc nữa nước mắt cho
others and deceiving others  If we&#39;ve reached the end of the night, then
kẻ rồi lừa người ta đã quê đêp thôi thì
let go to ease your heart. A
hãy buông đến cho nhẹ lòng Thạnh Xuân
girl&#39;s youth is very difficult, you know? People
của người con gái ngăn lắm em biết
and you are like this. Your
không Người ta với em thế nào sa ương
beauty has fallen. PH, I see all the heavy troubles shining
sắc em PH muu anh thấy muôn phiền nặng
on your melancholy eyes. The happy day will come.
chiếu trên đôi mắt em u sầu ngày vui đến
How many times have you been by my side, sad and uninvited, why do they
bên em bao lần ngy buồn không mời sao cứ
always come so quickly? When will the roses of life ring? Hey, you&#39;re not alone.
bao giờ kh l em này em không một mình
Please stop crying. Tears
đâu em thôi đi đừng khóc nữa nước mắt
for others. People will go home for the night, then let
cho kh rồi người ta đ quê đêm thôi thì
go.  To ease the heart of a
hãy buông để cho nhẹ lòng thh xuân của
girl&#39;s youth Ngan, you know, a
người con gái Ngân lắm em biết
girl&#39;s youth is very
không thanh xuân của người con
difficult,
gái ngăn
you know? [
lắm em biết
Music]
[âm nhạc]
together in the future is my
cùng bên nhau mai sau là điều ước muốn
biggest wish. My hand is outstretched like a
lớn nhất bàn tay anh đưa ra tựa là năng
song.  This sparkling, vast space
ngâm lấp lanh này không gian bao la
belongs to only one person, we give love
thuộc về cho riêng ai ta cho tình yêu
Hundred Years of flowers and so many sweet dreams that
Trăm Năm n hoa biết bao giấc mơ ngọt
were difficult to give birth overnight, love and
ngào đã từng khó sinh qua đêm tình mộng
pillows were wet. His tightness seemed to be filled with
gối đã ướt Đớm chật anh như hẹt qua ngập
warmth. The Morning Sun even though  The two of us are gone and
tràn ấm áp Nắng Sớm dù hai ta ra đi và
even though we&#39;re gone, this stork reflects on
dù hai ta ra đi vần cò này bóng ra ngày
that day an old thing that I could never wish to pass and
ấy một điều xá xưa ta thể nguyện qua rồi
go together for a thousand years from now,
cùng đi cùng đi ngàn năm về sau mình vẫn
we&#39;ll still love each other. The color of love blossoms and
nhau T màu lên traii hoa tình yêu chúng
we&#39;re suddenly gone.  Hold out the one that still resonates and
mình đột t mặt giơ một kia còn vang vá
don&#39;t let go of the hand that stabs double stabs double b d and
không buông bàn tay đâm đôi đâm đôi b d
you and I will overcome it and bring it. The next night
là anh cùng em vượt qua mà đem Tối
Cuong Khi stepped over each number
ngoài khơi biể xanh Trạch cao đầy dố lớ
The land beyond
phiêu r cùng nhau mở l đu đất phía
[music]
[âm nhạc]
after
sau
the future is the
cùng mên nhau mai sau là điều ước muốn
biggest wish my hand holds out like this
lớn nhất bàn tay anh đưa ra tựa là năng
sparkling sound energy, this vast space belongs
âm lấp lanh này không gian bao la thộc
to each one of us for the love of a Hundred Years
về cho riêng ai ta cho tình yêu Trăm Năm
n  So many sweet dreams that used to be
n hoa biết bao giấc mơ ngọt ngào đã từng
difficult to communicate through the night of love, dreams and wet pillows
khó xh qua đêm tình mộng gối đa ướt cm
Suddenly I feel like the past summer is filled with sound Austria is
Chợt anh như hè qua ngập tràn âm Áo đang
early Even though we&#39;re gone and even though we&#39;re gone, there&#39;s
sớm dù hai ta ra đi và dù hai ta ra đi
still the shadow of that day, one thing  Far away, we
vẫn cò đây bóng giá ngày ấy một điều xa
pray to pass and then go together for
xất ta để nguyện qua rồi cùng đi cùng đi
thousands of years, we will be with each other and
ngàn năm về sau mình vần Có
color the desert, our love is
Nhau tô màu lắ traii hoang tình yêu
forever gone, but the grave still echoes and I don&#39;t let
đậc tan màt gi mộ kia còn vang vá không
go of the hand that makes love to each other B D is you
buông bàn tay đm đôi đm đôi B D là anh
and me  Let&#39;s go through it with you. That night
lại anh cùng em vượt qua mà đem Tối
when I passed through each fish living off the coast of the
kia khế cầng khi Đạ qua từng con sống s
blue lake, Trach Cao, Strawberry Leaf
ngoài khơi bể xanh Trạch cao đời dâu lá
Adventure, together we opened up the pain of a single thing
phiêu r cùng nhau mở l đau đơn việc
[music]
[âm nhạc]
after [
sau
Laughter]
[Tiếng cười]
[sound]  music] let&#39;s
[âm nhạc]
go together after a thousand years, we&#39;ll still
cùng đi cùng đi ngàn năm về sau mình vẫn
have
có
each other T the color of leaves and flowers, the love inside
nhau T màu lá traii hoa tình yêu trong
us has melted, but holding out the other side, Vong and
mình đã tan mà giơ bù kia còn Vông vá
countless hands are immersed in the couple&#39;s dress, I&#39;m
không muông bàn tay đắm đuôi đầm đôi m d
you, I&#39;m you, I&#39;ll go through it together  That dark night,
là anh là anh cùng em vượt qua mà đêm
when I passed by, I lived
kia kế cầng khi đ qua th con sống s
off the coast of a green lake in a high farm, my family
ngoài khơi bể xanh trạ cao đời dâu lớ
wandered together somewhere to write
phiêu g cùng nhau ơ l đâu đ viếtc
[music]
[âm nhạc]
s
s
now I have someone to
phải chắng lúc này em có mộtn người thế
replace them?  Give me a lot, you&#39;re morning, night,
thay họ cho em nhiều Biên em sớm tối
evening, and I
luộng chiều còn anh chỉ
&#39;m just like a stranger, fleeting through the
là giống như người lạ Thoáng Qua
path to the
Đạo đến tận
end, but still old and
cùng nhưng vẫn già và hạnh
happy, right now, it&#39;s all just a dream
phúc phải chí bây giờ tất cả chỉ là giấc
[music]
[âm nhạc]
dreaming of loving someone waiting for you to go  I also
mơ một thương ai chờ em đi anh cũng
didn&#39;t
không
expect to be sick when my mouth was lonely, I was alone, I was with you for so
ngờ đành ốm khi miệng Cô Đơn Mình Anh
many years, I loved you without any
đê năm tháng ê đê Yêu em chẳng cần đọng
reason, but you let go of my hand and then I was
đế vậy mà em nỡ buông tay anh rồi buồn
sad, I cried, I complained to the
đau anh khóc anh than với
heavens about my broken heart, why did I receive
trời thương thất lòng sao anh nhận lại
nothing in return?  It&#39;s like I can see
không nhành hoa Thy l như đ thấy lòng
why my heart keeps wondering
sao tim anh không ngừng nhớ
when will I forget the person
mong đến bao giờ mới quên được người
I
mình
love [
yêu
just have to say
phải chỉ bay
that everything is just a dream just a
rằng tất cả Chỉ Là Giấc Mơ Chỉ Là Giấc
dream A stranger waiting for you to go  I also
Mơ Một thướng ngi chờ em đi anh cũng
didn&#39;t
không
expect to have to hug her. She was alone with me and her for
ngờ đành ôm ki Niệm cô đng mình anh với
many years. Loving you doesn&#39;t have to be
đê năm tháng em đê Yêu em chẳng cần đóng
so difficult, but you let go of my hand and then I&#39;m
đến vậy mà em nỡ buông tay anh rồi buồn
sad. I cry. I complain to
đau anh khóc anh than với
God. How can I get my diploma back
trời thương thất lòng sao anh nhận lại
so
bằng
quickly?  Hoa Thay is like you see, my
kh nhanh Hòa Thay l như em thấy lòng sao
heart keeps wondering how long it will take to
tim anh không ngừng nhớ
forget the person I
mau đến bao giờ mới quên được người mình
love, but I can&#39;t bear to let go of your hand and then I&#39;m
yêu vậy mà em nỡ buông tay anh rồi buồn
sad, I cry, I complain to God, my
đau anh khóc anh than với
heart is broken, why do I get it back
trời thương thất lòng sao anh nhận lại
quickly?  Instead, I feel like my heart is
nhanh ho thay l như thấy lòng sao tim
constantly
anh không ngừng mong
wondering when will I forget the person I love
nhớ đến bao giờ mới quên được người mình
[music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]
I will never forget the
yêu chẳng bao giờ anh quên được
person I loved
người
[music]
[âm nhạc]
who left without  Say a word for me to
người đi mà chẳng nói một lời để anh
play with in the middle of life. The words of love are now
chơi với giữa dòng đời lời yêu sau nay
too far away.
quá xa
Words of Love now I still silently
rồi Lời Thương giờ n cũng lặng
refuse to accept the news that you are about to live with the
chối nhận tin em sắp sống bên
person you love for the rest of my
người mà em thương yêu đến cuối
life. My heart aches. Oh,
đời lòng anh như đau thắt Em
how can I say goodbye?
ơi làm sao để lễ thôi ngừng
stop, today I&#39;m happy, I&#39;m with the
rơ Hôm nay em hạnh phúc rồi em đã bên
person I
người mà lòng em
love, I forgot the promise, the wife, I promised the
yêu em quên câu hẹn câu thê em hứa với
person who would love me for the rest of my life. My
người cả đời thương
love is only short, why do I
em Em ơi chữa tình ngắn thôi mà sao anh
have to drag it along for the rest of my
phải kéo theo một
life? I now have a couple.  As for me, I&#39;m so
đời em ơi Em giờ có đôi còn anh thì phải
reasonable.
lẽ lii thật rồi
When I promised in the past, I wouldn&#39;t eat anything like ginger, C
khi xưa hứa chẳng cánh raa gừng C muôi
salty spoons, and don&#39;t want silk,
mặn chẳng ham lụa
but today, Pink Dress with Brocade and Flowers of Love. In the past, you really
la hôm nay Áo Hồng Gấm Hoa Tình Xưa
paid me back.
người trả hết anh thật
[music]
[âm nhạc]
You left without saying a
người đi mà chẳng nói một
word and let me play.  In the midst of this
lời để anh chơi với giữa dòng
life, the words of love are so far
đời lời yêu nay sao quá xa
away. Words of love are now silent as I
xôi Lời Thương giờ n cũng lặng
receive the news that you are about to live with the person you
chố nhận tin em sắp sống bên người mà em
love until the end of your life. My heart aches. Dear,
thương yêu đến cuôi đời lòng anh như đau
how can I stop the ceremony?
ơi làm sao để lễ thôi ngừng
Today I am happy.  Luckily, I&#39;m with
rơ Hôm nay em hạnh phúc rồi em đã bên
the person I
người mà lòng em
love. I forgot the promise and the oath. I promise to love you for the
yêu em quên cấu hẹn cấu thề em hứa với
rest of my life.
người cả đời thương
My love is only short, so why do I
em Em ơi chữa tình ngắn thôi mà sao anh
have to drag it along for a
phải kéo theo một
lifetime? You&#39;re now married and I&#39;m the one who&#39;s being
đời em ơi Em giờ có đôi còn anh thì phải
reasonable.  It&#39;s true,
lẽ loi thật
in the past, I promised never to leave, ginger,
rồi khi xưa hứa chẳng cánh xa gừng cây
salty, white, silk,
muôi mặn trẳng ham lụa
today&#39;s Pink Dress with Brocade Flowers, Love is
la hôm nay Áo Hồng Gấm Hoa Tình xương
completely paid to me, my
người trả hết anh thật
love is only short, why do I
à em ơi chữa tình ngắn thôi mà sao anh
have to drag it along, my dear, you have it now
phải kéo theo một đơ ơi em ơi em giờ có
couple and you are reasonable. Lyrics poem
đôi còn anh thì phải lẽ lii thơ X khi
music]
[âm nhạc]
really
thật
There is someone who loves you more than yourself,
Có một người từng yêu anh hơn chính mình
there is someone who always values ​​love
có một người mà luôn coi trọng chữ tình
by your side and sees you as
ở bên anh mà xem anh như tất
everything, but today I
cả nhưng hôm nay em mới nhận
realized that until now, I also have you by my side.
ra đến bây giờ thì bên anh cũng có
Who has another person who will replace me?
ai có thêm một người sẽ thay em lên thếm
V I don&#39;t understand what I did.
V em chẳng hiểu em đã làm gì
Xi left. Don&#39;t say pity.
xi rời raa Em đừng nói câu Thương Hại
Loving someone who cheats is honestly not
yêu một người gian dối thật lòng chẳng
happy. That&#39;s all. Today
thấy vui tình cảm mình thế thôi hôm nay
I love someone else.
anh yêu người khác rồi anh buông lời xin
Apologize that our team is not a good match so we need
lỗi đội mình chẳng dứng đôi nên cần
someone new, we have to break up, you&#39;re
người mới thôi anh ơi ta phải chia đ anh
no longer the same as before, you&#39;re no longer the same.
chẳng còn như trước cũng chẳng còn vẫn
Now the king and the new person who loves you can see each other hand in
Vương giờ cùng người mớii thương tay
hand on the same road, then you&#39;ll be
trông tay trên một con đường thôi thì
happy. I hope you.  Isn&#39;t it
hạnh phúc nhé hy vọng anh dẽ không không
like we had to share
phải như chúng ta hôm nay đã phải chia
Xá
Xá
[music] today? By
[âm nhạc]
now, there&#39;s no one else with me who
đến bây giờ thì bên anh cũng có
will see you rise.
ai có thêm một người sẽ thấy em lên thế
B
B
I don&#39;t understand what I did
em chẳng hiểu em đã làm gì
wrong, leave me, don&#39;t say anything.  Thuong Hai
sai rời xa em đừng nói câu Thương Hại
loves someone for a fake price, I honestly don&#39;t
yêu một người giá dối thật lòng chẳng
feel happy with my feelings, that&#39;s all, today
thấy vui tình cảm mình thế thôi hôm nay
I love someone else, I&#39;m
anh yêu người khác rồi anh buông lời xin
sorry, I&#39;m not a good match, so I need someone to pretend,
lỗi đi mình chẳng dứng đôi nên cần người
I have to share, I&#39;m no
mã thôi anh ơi ta phải chia đố anh chẳng
longer the same as before  It&#39;s not like Vuong is
còn như trước cũng chẳng còn vẫn Vương
now holding hands with her new lover,
giờ cùng người mới thương tay trông tay
just walking on the same road will be happy.
trên một con đường thôi thì hạnh phúc
I hope you won&#39;t be like
nhé Hy phọng anh sẽ không không phải như
us today, having to separate and love
chúng ta hôm nay đã phải chia xa yêu một
someone who is willing to give up and honestly doesn&#39;t feel happy in
người sẵn xối thật lòng chẳng thấy vui
love.  That&#39;s just me, today you love
tình cảm mình thế thôi hôm nay anh yêu
someone else and then you apologize and say
người khác rồi anh buông lời xin lỗi nói
you&#39;re not compatible so you need someone new, honey, we
mình chẳng sứng đôi nên cần người mới
have to share, you&#39;re no
thôi anh ơi ta phải chia đố anh chẳng
longer the same as before, you&#39;re no longer the same. Now the king
còn như trước cũng chẳng còn vẫn Vương
and the new person love each other, looking after each other.
giờ cùng người mới thương tay trông tay
Just one path and you&#39;ll be happy. I hope you wo
trên một con đường thôi thì hạnh phúc
n&#39;t be like
nhé Hy phọng anh sẽ không không phải như
us today who had to separate,
chúng ta hôm nay đã phải chia xa không
not like us today who have to
phải như chúng ta hôm nay
criticize
chiê
[music]
[âm nhạc]
x
x
hard to wish for more beauty Ivory  The two of us
khó khi ước nào đẹp hơn Ngà đôi ta bắt
started to feel more pain as soon as we were
đầu cô đớn đau nào nặng hơn ngay mình xa
apart,
nhau
which eyes were sadder than the eyelids You let out sadness,
có đôi mắt nào buồn hơn bơm Mí Em tuôn
nothing is more bitter than you quickly fade
sầu có đắng cy nào bằng em vôi vàng qua
away What kind of person is the man walking next to you who is
mau người đàn ông đang đi bên bên em là
afraid of you?  I don&#39;t love you, I don&#39;t
nào sợ người ta không yêu thương em anh
know
biết phải làm
what to do if one day the person you love cheats on you, you
sao nếu một ngày người em yêu bôi bà em
don&#39;t need the bright things if this bride will
đừng cần những thứ cao sáng nếu dâu này
leave in a hurry I&#39;m still waiting for you to hide it, I
họ Xẽ đi vội vàng anh vẫn chờ em giấu
know you love that person so much I
biết em thương người ấy đã rật nhiều anh
ask  How many hearts do you have in my heart?
hỏi lòng anh có bao nhiêu trái tim em
Now I have forgotten the flow. Please don&#39;t forget that we
giờ đã quên luồng chiều Xin đừng quên ta
loved each other. It hurts so much. Do you know? I
yêu người là bạnh đau lắm em có biết
sit and long for it. Some
không từng Ngà ngồi nhớ mong để rồi Vài
corners of my life, the
ngóc trong từ kỳ niềm chất chiều
rain still falls in my afternoons.  Sitting here
mưa còn rơi những chiều anh ngồi đây cô
alone, I love you, I love you, I
liêu người đơn Anh An yêu em những
have no memory more beautiful than the day we
l có ký ức nào đẹp hơn ngày đôi ta bắt
started to be lonely, no pain worse than the moment we were
đầu cô đơn đau nào nặng hơn ngay mình xa
apart, no sadder eyes than the tears in my eyes, how
nhau có đôi mắt nào buồn hơn bơm m em
bitter is that?  How can you pass quickly?
tuôn s có đắng cy nào bằng em vôi vàng
What kind of person is the man walking next to you?
người như thế
Now people don&#39;t love you. I
nào giờ người ta không yêu thương em anh
know
biết phải làm
what to do if one day the person you love
sao nếu một ngày người em yêu Bội bà em
won&#39;t need the things you crave. If in the future
đừng cần những thứ khao xá Nếu sau nay
they  I&#39;ll leave in a hurry I&#39;m still waiting for you to hide it  Do you
họ sẽ đi vội vàng anh vẫn chờ em giấu
know? I&#39;m
yêu đâu anh nh anh kh C em C biết không
sorry, it hurts
C lỗi đau đ hng
[music]
[âm nhạc]
deep
sâu
If one day the person you love Boi Bac, you
Nếu một ngày người em yêu Bội Bạc em
don&#39;t need expensive things. If deep now they
đừng cần những thứ cao xa nếu sâu nay họ
leave in a hurry, I&#39;ll still wait for you to hold on. I
xa đi vội vàng anh vẫn chờ em giữ muôn M
know you love that person already.  very much I&#39;m
biết em thương người ấy đã rất nhiều Anh
satisfied you have so much heart
hài lòng anh có bao nhiêu trơi tim em
now I&#39;ve
giờ n quên thộc chin đừng qu ta đã từng
forgotten it  Who
yêu xin đừng
knows what will happen today,
tình yêu đâu ai biết trước đi gì nay
happiness tomorrow will be a
hạnh phúc mai thì biệt
long time apart, together like a long journey,
lý đậm sấu bên nhau như bước tương dày
even after two years. After breaking
cũng độ vớ sau hai tổi Chia
up, I moved on to someone
tay rồi anh đi theo người
new, and they have already left me.
mới người ta cũng đã bỏ
So today I have to
sờ Để hôm nay anh phải
cry and hug you to fix it.
khóc đi ôm em chốt được
No, don&#39;t cry, honey, don&#39;t be sad.
không Đừng khóc Anh Ơi Đừng
Don&#39;t cry. Don&#39;t
Buồn Giọt nước mắt ấy đừng
cry. Tell me
tu kể em nghe đi xem
what people have abandoned you.
nào người ta đã Bá anh
Why don&#39;t they truly love you? After all, you&#39;re
sao họ đâu thương anh thật lòng mà sau
still alive. Hurry up and I
anh vẫn còn đời
love you
Mau còn em yêu anh chân
sincerely. Why are you dying?
thành tại sao anh nm mỡ rơi
[music]
[âm nhạc]
hem
hem
then I followed the
rồi anh đi theo người
dreamer and they left
mơ người ta cũng đã bỏ
me. So today I have to
sớ Để hôm nay anh phải
ask for a hug. Don&#39;t cry. Do
kh đòi ôm em chú được kh
n&#39;t be sad. Don&#39;t cry. Do
đừng khóp Anh Ơi Đừng
n&#39;t cry.
Buồn Giọt nước mắt ấy đừng
Tell me about those tears.
tu kể em nghe đi xem
No matter how people left you,
nào người ta đã bỏ anh
why did they leave? I love you and feel
sao họ đâu Thương anh thất
disappointed, but after that I still have a life, I hope
lòng mà sau anh vẫn còn đời
you still love me.
thành tại sao anh n mỏ rơi
I&#39;m sorry, why did my
hem đừng khóc Anh Ơi Đừng
eyes fall? Don&#39;t cry, Honey, don&#39;t be sad. Don&#39;t let those tears leak out. Tell
Buồn Giọt nước mắt ấy đừng
me.
tuồn kể em nghe đi xem
No matter how people left you far away and
nào người ta đã bã anh
loved you
đu thương anh thật
sincerely, why are you still alive? I still love you. I sincerely love you,
lòng mà sao anh vẫn còn đời
why did you leave me? You
thành tại sao anh n m rời
truly love me,
hết Còn em yêu anh chân
why do
thành tại sao
you
anh
say
n bố say
[music]
[âm nhạc]
you
em
old story Oh it&#39;s been so long but why are you
chuyện cũ Ơ qua lâu rồi mà sao em vẫn
still
còn
sad with tears in your eyes,
buồn còn nước mắt hoen mi
tears still heavy in your heart like
lệ còn nặng lòng hoài như
that people say you&#39;re not stupid and
thế người nói em chẳng ngu
sad but in the drunken night you shed tears and you said
buồn mà trong đêm say lệ tuốn và em nói
you chose to try to stand but now I can&#39;t do it  What&#39;s
em chọn cố đứng anh giờ chẳng thế làm gì
better than
tốt hơn
love? Who doesn&#39;t want to be with the person
tình yêu ai chẳng muốn ở bên người mà
they love? Going all the way, even though their day is my
mình thương cùng đi hết quãng Mường dù
daughter. My heart still has so many lingering
ngyt con gái anh Cương lòng vẫn còn bao
questions.
vấn
Honestly, I love you
vương thật lòng anh yêu rõ vết thương em
clearly. The wound you stabbed so deeply has made my heart ache. So
ghim thật sâu đã khiến tim u sông Vậy
now I  learn how to love someone I
giờ anh học cách đế yêu một người tôi
[music]
[âm nhạc]
love
thương
that story has passed a long time ago but why are you still
chuyện cũ ấy qua lâu rồi mà sao em vẫn
sad and your tears are
buồn còn nước mắt hoen mi
still so heavy that
lệ còn nặng lòng hoài như
people say you&#39;re not
thế người nói em chẳng ngu
stupid and sad in a drunken night  In my
buồn mà trong đêm say Lệ
eyes, you said you chose Co Don, I
tuống em nói em chọn Cố Đớn anh giờ
can&#39;t do anything better
chẳng thế làm gì tốt
than love. Who doesn&#39;t want to be with the person
hơn tình yêu ai chẳng muốn ở bên người
they love? It&#39;s been a long journey, even though it&#39;s my
mà mình thương cùng đi Hết quã đường dù
daughter. My heart is still there.
ng con gái anh Cương lòng vẫn còn bao
Truly, I love you clearly.  Loving you
Vương thật lòng anh yêu rõ vết thương em
really doesn&#39;t make my heart ache. So now
hu thật đâu đã khiến tim u sông Vậy giờ
I&#39;ve learned how to love someone with
anh học cách đế yêu một người tôn
dignity. Who doesn&#39;t want to be with the person
kỳ tình yêu ai chẳng muốn ở bên người mà
they love and go all the way with the
mình thương cùng đi hết quang đường dùng
girl I love so much that I still love you?
lịch con gái anh thương lòng vẫn còn bao
True King  I understand clearly that the wound that
Vương thật lòng anh hiểu rõ vết thương
hurt you was so deep that it made my heart sad
ướng em gìm thật sâu đã khiến tim u
So now I learn how to love someone who
sâ Vậy giờ anh học cách đế yêu một người
respects
tôn
me So now I learn how to love someone who will last forever
t Vậy giờ anh học cách đế yêu một
[music]
[âm nhạc]
a lifetime without singing  It&#39;s not a million times.
một đời không xướng trăm vạn lần
I have a needle so
đâu Em có kim nên đi bao u
I&#39;m going to be so sad and wrong. A minute ago, I
sầu sai lầm phút trước anh có ấn
regretted it. If I don&#39;t need it, please do
hận nếu đã không cần xin đừng bậ T
n&#39;t turn on. Who do I secretly love? Phuong is still there day and night. Surely it&#39;s not you. Is it true that my
ngày chắc không phải em có đúng như
small hands don&#39;t hold it?  I&#39;ve been
vậy đôi tay nhỏ bé không giữ anh
crying for a love that&#39;s right for
đa khóc thân cho một cuộc tình phải lýa
me, my dear, I can&#39;t help
ta Anh ơi Anh ơi Em nào có
but let go of your hand. I&#39;m in love with
thôi mà Sa anh nỡ buông tay em rồi trên
so much foolishness. The person I once
tình phùn phá sâu bao dại khờ Người Từng
loved is now breathing. Oh, is she as good
Thương Nhớ nay lại thở Ơ cô ta có tốt
as I hope?  Waiting to be far away from you, I&#39;m happier
như anh mong chờ xa em kh trắng anh hạnh
than a white girl. Love me for a
hơn một mái hoọ trắng thương anh thật
long time, don&#39;t forget me. I&#39;m still waiting for
lâu đừng quên em nhé Em vẫn chờ
[music]
[âm nhạc]
to open Who do you
mở
secretly love? Phuong is still there day and
Anh thương thầm ai Phương vẫn đêm
night. Surely it&#39;s not you. Are your
ngày chắc không phải em có đúng như
small hands like that?  Keep me
vậy đôi tay nhỏ bé không giữ anh
crying for a love that has to
được khóc thân cho một cuộc tình phải
end, my dear, why are you so
lệa ta anh ơi anh ơi thêm nào có
guilty that you let go of my hand and the
tội mà sao anh nỡ buông tay em rồi
love story is ruined? After so many fools, the
chuyện tình vụn phá Sau bao dại khờ
one who once loved you is now breathing
Người Từng Thương Nhớ nay lại thở
Oh, is she as good as you?  What do you expect? Are you
Ơ cô ta có tốt như anh mong chờ gi Em có
sure I&#39;m happier than a family? They don&#39;t
chắc anh hạnh phúc hơn một mái họ chá
really love you.
thương anh thật
Don&#39;t forget me. I&#39;m still waiting for you. Dear brother. I don&#39;t have it.
lòng đừng quên em nhé Em vẫn chờ m Anh
How can you let
ơi Anh ơi Em nào có thôi mà sao anh nỡ
go of my hand? After all the
buông tay em rồi trên tình phùn phá Sau
foolishness,  The person I once loved and missed is actually there.
khờ Người Từng Thương Nhớ nay lại thật
She&#39;s as good as you. What do you expect? I&#39;m
có T cô tốt như anh mong chờ gi em cô
sure you&#39;ll be happy forever.
chắc anh hạnh phúc
They love you so
a một mãi họ tráng thương anh thật
much. Don&#39;t forget me. I&#39;m still waiting. Dreaming of
lò đừng quên em nhé Em vẫn chờ
a white woman who loves you truly.
Mơ một m h trắng thương anh thật
Don&#39;t forget me.
lòng đừng quên em
I&#39;m
nhé Em
Still Waiting
Vẫn Chờ
[music]
[âm nhạc]
I love an ordinary person
Anh yêu lấy một người bình thường để đêm
so that at night I&#39;ll whisper how much I miss you, even though this life
về thì thầm nhớ thương mặc cuộc đời này
is in the past and even in the present, all
sao cũng được ở quá khứ và cả Hiện tại
love is weak and no
yêu thương nào cũng nhạt cũng phải chẳng
one can sit with anyone all night.
ai ngồi cùng ai được hết đêm
[music]
[âm nhạc]
long, first love is like a miracle
dài chếc tình đầu ban sơ như phép nhiệm
until you meet someone
mâu cho đến khi em gặp người
behind the gentle sunshine, gentle sleep,
sau nắng nhẹ nhàng êm êm giấc ngủ dịu xa
else, hot and lost, following the sad wind of
khác nóng lạc đường đi theo cơn gió tâm
many nights calling your name  Makes my heart
thương bao đêm nhắc tên khiến lòng tồn
linger for hundreds of years of lunar vows that keep turning late, let
thương những thề Nguyệt trăm năm cứ hóa
go, let my heart be at
muộn phiên buông bỏ đi cho lòng bình
peace, let me love an ordinary person, and at
yên tha yêu lấy một người bình thường để
night whisper and miss
đêm về thì thầm nhớ thương mặc cuộc đời
this life, no matter what,
này sao cũng
past and present, Love
được quá khứ và cả Hiện tại Yêu Thương
Even if it&#39;s boring, no one can sit
Nào cùng nhạt cũng phải chẳng ai ngồi
with anyone all night long. Who lies and
cùng ai được hết đêm dài ai dối trá và
who is sincere doesn&#39;t matter anymore.
ai thật lòng chẳng quan trọng nữa rồi
If there&#39;s no place left with peace, the tree
phải không nời nào còn bình yên thì cây
will search in the blink of an eye for the night of Sui Tien, the night of the
sẽ mò ngay nhắp mắt cho đêm Tùy Tiền đêm
rain, heavy things for Hien.  asking
mưa về đồ nặng mái Hiền hỏi lòng người
if there is peace in people&#39;s hearts
liệu có bình
[music] peace and sunshine,
[âm nhạc]
lost in the wind, lost in the wind,
nắng lạc đường đi theo cơn gió tâm
many nights of sadness, mentioning the name makes the heart linger over
thương bao đêm nhắc tên khiến lòng tồn
the vows of a hundred years of moon turning into sadness and
thương những thề Nguyệt trăm năm cứ hóa
sadness, leaving the heart at peace
muộn phiền buồ bỏ đi cho lòng bình
[music] peace,
[âm nhạc]
my love  Marry a normal person to
yên ta yêu lấy một người bình thường để
whisper and miss at night, no matter
đêm về thì thầm nhớ thương mặc cuộc đời
how much this life
này sao cũng
is in the past and in the present, no matter how
được ở quá khứ và cả Hiện tại Yêu Thương
weak love is, no one can sit
Nào cùng nhạt cũng phải chẳng ai ngồi
with anyone all night long, no one lies and
cùng ai được hết đêm dài ai dối trả và
no one is sincere.  More importantly,
ai thật lòng chẳng quan trọng nữa rồi
if there is no
phải không
place where there is peace, the trees will fade away and
nơi nào còn bình yên thì cây sẽ mờ ngay
close their eyes for the night. Sui Tien, the rainy night,
nhắm mắt cho đêm Tùy Tiền đêm mưa về đồ
heavy things, the eaves ask people&#39;s hearts if they are at
nặng mái hiên hỏi lòng người liệu có
peace and love to marry an ordinary person, so that at night, they will
yên yêu lấy một người bình thường để đêm
whisper and miss me.  How can this life
về thì thầm nhớ thương m cuộc đời này
be in the past and in the Present? No
được ở quá khứ và cả Hiện tại Yêu Thương
matter how boring love is, no one can sit
Nào cùng nhạt cũng phải chẳng ai ngồi
with anyone all night
cùng ai được hết đêm
long. Whoever sulks and who is sincere doesn&#39;t
dài ai dỗi trả và ai thật lòng chẳng
matter anymore, right? There&#39;s no place left for
quan trọng nữa rồi phải không nơi nào
peace.  I will
còn bình yên thì cây sẽ
immediately close my eyes for the night of Sui Tien, the night of the
màu ngay nhắm mắt cho đêm Tùy Tiền đêm
rain, heavy things on the eaves,
mưa về đồ nặng mái hiênn
asking if people&#39;s hearts are at
hỏi lòng người lệu có bình
peace, asking if people&#39;s hearts
yên hỏi lòng người lệu
are at peace.
có bình
[music] [Applause] [
[âm nhạc]
there is a path to happiness  The happiness we&#39;ve been through
có con đường hạnh phúc đôi tha từng bước
has come and gone, it&#39;s time to tell you my story
qua cũng đã đến lúc kể thước anh
You&#39;ve changed three streams of love
à Anh đã thay đổi ba lửa suối tình cảm
for a long time, maybe your heart doesn&#39;t want to do that I
bấy lâu có lẽ thăm tâm anh chẳng muốn
miss you, miss the cycle, miss the
đâu Em thấy nhớ anh nhớ vòng thaay nhớ
moments, miss the adorations
khoảnh khắc từng đóm dày nhớ những chầu
Smiling and having fun under that thatched roof Hey, peace and wine, I
núa vui đùa dưới mái tranh Ê rượu bình
love you so much. Similar to the body that
yên thương anh nhiều lắm Tương tấm thân
caused the first death, seeing you in pain,
gây môn sơ xác lụi tà thấy anh đớn đâu
I can&#39;t stand it.
em đâu chịu được
Yesterday you were there. Today, when I get home,
n Hôm qua anh cò nơi đó Hôm nay tan về
I&#39;ll play in the middle of the night.
nơi đó em chơi vâ giữa đêm Tho hơi thời
Time is so sad and sad, he is the whole world, the
gian sàu lắm â sầu anh ấy là cả thế giới
whole sky of the future This song has no
là cả bầu trời tương lai bài này chẳng
one left by my side shaking me every day in
còn một ai bên cạnh em lắc l mỗi ngày
this life I&#39;m sorry I can&#39;t
kiếp này Chỗ em xin lỗi chẳng thể bước
walk with you for the rest of my life to see  Every
đi cùng anh đi hết cuộc đời để xem mỗi
time the fate of An Unfulfilled Love
lầng duên liệu có An Bài Tình Yêu Không
comes back, I keep it deep in my heart. If I
Trọn về nữa em đem cất sâu vào tim kiếp
meet again in the next life, I won&#39;t hesitate to shake you. It
sau có xuyên gặp lại em chẳng nể lắc mất
hurts
anh đau
[music]
[âm nhạc]
I miss you, miss your arms, miss the
em thấy nhớ anh nhớ vòng tay nhớ khoảnh
moments in long stretches.  The people
khắc từng đám dài nhớ những trồng ng vui
playing happily under the thatched roof Oh, peaceful wine, I
đùa dưới mái tranh Ê rượu bình yên
love you so much. The similarity between my body and my life caused my
thương anh nhiều lắm Tương tấm thân gây
soul to fade away. Seeing you in pain, I can&#39;t
MN sơ xác lụi tà thấy anh đớn đâu em đâu
stand it.
chịu được
Yesterday you were still there. Today, when I melt, I return to the place where it
n Hôm qua anh còn nơi đó Hôm nay tan về
hurts. I play with you.  Autumn night,
nơi đau em chơi với giữa đêm Thu hơi
time, deep sadness, he is the whole
thời gian sâu lắm âu sầu anh ấy là cả
world, the whole sky, the future, tomorrow, there will be
thế giới là cả B trời tương lai mai này
no one by my side to shake me every
chẳng còn một ai bên cạnh em lắc l mỗi
day in this life, I&#39;m sorry I can&#39;t
ngày kiếp này cho em xin lỗi chẳng thể
walk with you for the rest of my life  Let&#39;s see if
bước đi cùng anh đi hết cuộc đời để xem
every ounce of Fate has an Unfulfilled Love Arrangement,
mỗi lng Duyên liệu có An Bài Tình Yêu
I&#39;ll keep it deep in my heart. I&#39;ll
Không Trọn về nữa em đem cất sâu vào tim
see you again in the next life. I won&#39;t
kiếp sau có xuyên gặp lại em chẳng để
lose you yesterday. Yesterday you were there.
lắc mất anh đ Hôm qua anh còn nơi đó Hôm
Today, I&#39;ve gone somewhere else. I&#39;ll play with you now.  It&#39;s a
nay tan về nơi đâu em chơi với giờa đêm
slow night and the world is so sad. He
thâ hơi thế gian sàu lắm ông dầ anh ấy
&#39;s the whole world, the whole sky. The future,
là cả thế giới là cả bầu trời tương lai
tomorrow, and tomorrow there&#39;s no one left by my side. Oh,
mai này chẳng còn một ai bên cạnh em
every day, I
lắng o mỗi ngày kếp này cho em xin lỗi
&#39;m sorry. I can&#39;t walk with you for the rest of my
chẳng thể bước đi cùng anh đi hết cuộc
life.  Let&#39;s see if each good fate will come
đời K xem mỗi lương duyên liệu có ơ bài
back in the song &quot;Love Is Not Perfect&quot; I&#39;ll take C deep
Tình Yêu Không Trọn về nữa em đem C sâu
into my heart if I see you again often I
vào tim kép sâu có xuyên gặp lại em
won&#39;t be afraid to lose you if I
chẳng nể lắc mất anh
see you again I
đâu kép sâu có xuyên gặp
won&#39;t let you die Lạc MT
lại em chẳng để Lặc MT người thô
[music]  ]
[âm nhạc]
a
a
Let me know if I&#39;m right or
Hãy cho anh biết anh Giờ đang đúng hay
wrong now, why do
sai mà sao cô
n&#39;t you, my heart keeps remembering the
chớ tim của anh cứ nhớ hoài nhớ những kỷ
unhappy memories, I miss the person who hurt
niệm không vui nhớ một người tốn thương
me, he passed by, so I make my own heart,
mình là anh qua ngóc nên tự làm trái tim
no one else  Mention your name right
đầ đừng ai nhắc đến tên của em ngay lúc
now, no one will ask how I am now,
này đừng ai hỏi đến anh giờ đây như thế
still cold, not loving anyone, still going home
nào vẫn lãnh lùng chẳng yêu ai vẫn đi về
alone, only looking for acquaintances
chí một mình chỉ biết tìm quen vào những
when I&#39;m busy Let me drink just once to
lúc anh xây Hãy cho anh uống một lần để
make me incredibly drunk.  I need to let you cry just
được say đến bất cần để cho anh khóc một
once to ease the pain you&#39;ve been feeling so
lần cho nhẹ vời đi nỗi lòng anh đã ra vờ
hard that your heart is so strong that no
mạnh mẽ đến tim mình vớii cố đờ để chẳng
one can see that you&#39;re still hurting for the raindrops
ai thấy anh vẫn đang tốn thương hạt mưa
like crying for someone, why do the raindrops keep falling in
như khóc một người sao hạt mưa cứ Rớ
need of someone Hieu  cradle of love, giving,
hoài cần ai đó Hiếu nôi lò TM sự cho với
sadness,
nỗi buồn
going all the way, loving you, my heart
đi hết quang đường yêu đứa trái tim mình
still has a life, I was wrong to put it all away
vẫn có đời l anh đã sai khi tô trôi tất
to truly love you
cả để thật lòng yêu
[music]
[âm nhạc]
Don&#39;t let anyone
đừng ai nhắc
mention your name right now, don&#39;t let anyone  Ask
đến tên của em ngay lúc này đừng ai hỏi
him how he is now, still
đến anh giờ đây như thế nào vẫn lạnh
cold and doesn&#39;t love anyone, still going home alone,
lùng chẳng yêu ai vẫn đi về chí một mình
only knowing how to forget the times when he&#39;s gone,
Chỉ biết timm quên vào những lúc anh x
letting him not once to be the Emperor,
để cho anh không một lần để được xâ Đế
not caring about letting him not once, to be gentle with you
Bất cần để cho anh không một lần cho nhẹ
Going through my heart, I pretended to be strong, kept quiet and
vớii đi nỗi lòng anh đã ra vờ mạnh mẽ đế
numb so that no one could see that I
im mình với vô đờ để chẳng ai thấy anh
was still loving the raindrops like crying for
vẫn đang tốt thương hạt mưa như khóc một
someone, why did the raindrops keep falling and I
người sao hạt mưa cứ rớt hoài
needed someone to love me? The monk gave me
cần ai đó hếu nôi l TM sư cho với nỗi
all the joy.  In love,
vui đi hết quan đường yêu đương trái tim
my heart still has a single thing: I was wrong to give
mình vẫn có đơn là anh đã sai khi tự
up everything to truly love
chôi tất cả để thật lòng yêu
you. Give me one chance to make it so I
em Hãy cho anh ốn một lần để được xây
can&#39;t understand it so I can feel better. Say
đến bất cơ để cho anh khó ng mân cho nhẹ
I did.  Pretending to be strong enough to
ngườii đi Nói l anh đã ra vờ mạnh mẽ đến
trust my girlfriend so that no one would see that I&#39;m
tì mình với cô đời để chẳng ai thấy anh
still loving him so much, it&#39;s like crying for
vẫn đang tốt thương hàt ngưa như khóc
someone, why do raindrops keep falling, I need
một người sao hạt mưa cứ rớt hoài cần ai
someone to confide in. Hieu Noi Lo still feels sad
đó Hiếu Nội Lò tâm sự cho vẫ nỗi buồn đi
all the way to love left.  My heart
hết quang đường yêu đương trái tim mình
still
vẫn vỗ
flutters that I was wrong to
đờ là anh đã sai khi từ
refuse everything
chối tất
[music]
[âm nhạc]
even
cả
to truly
để thật
love
lòng yêu
you
em
[music]
[âm nhạc]
e
e
ten thousand words of
vạn lời yêu
love will end after two words divided into a
thương cũng hết sau hai từ chia
thousand promises
thay ngàn lời hứa
I will love you forever  I also fly back with the wind.
Xẽ yêu Yu mãi cũng theo gió bay về chời
I don&#39;t want to cry. Just because I regret the
Anh có muốn khóc đâu Chỉ vì tiếc nối cho
days we spent
những tháng ngày mình bên
together, time has erased the pain. I
nhau thời gian có xoa mờ Niềm
wonder if
Đau liệu rằng duyên
fate will forgive me. My
số có thứ tha cho mình không
happy friend,
é người bạn hạnh phúc
I would sell it to get a pension.
ta bán đi đổi lấy hưu qu
If you can, please don&#39;t hurt each other
xua Nếu như có thể xin đừng làm nhau
because life is
đau vì cuộc đời dài
so long, who knows what tomorrow will bring
ngàn ai biết ngày mai
?  It&#39;s bittersweet in the
lần mất nhau C đắng muôn
next life, but we&#39;ll never be together again. The
phà kiếp sau hưa sẽ bên nhau bí được
pain in our body is still too much.
kh vết thương xác th đau rồi còn quá
So how can our feelings hurt? The
Mau vậy tình cảm ta cháu đau rồi làm sao
heart wants to say a
khơ Trái Tim Muốn Nói một
word that I want to be with you for the rest of my
lờn muốn bên em suốt cuộc
life. Love each other in the last life.
đời chót thương nhau ở kiếp
Hey, please don&#39;t go
nà xin đừng hẹn kiếp
away [music]
xa
Will fate
liệu rằng duyên số
forgive me? My
có thứ tha cho mình không
happy friend
é người bạn hạnh
I sold in exchange for my retirement.
phúc ta bán đi đổi lấy hưu qu
Do you regret it just because of a few
anh em có nuôi tiếc không chỉ vì đôi
impatient moments?  dreaming of someone who has
phút nóng lòng mà đánh mơ người đã có
the whole city of Xan with me
với mình cả thành
If possible, please don&#39;t hurt each other
Xân Nếu Như như có thể xin đừng làm nhau
because life is
đau vì cuộc đời dài
long, who knows tomorrow
ngàn ai biết ngày mai
? No one can live through
Sa có ai sống qua một
losing each other once. It&#39;s
lần mất nhau C đắng muôn
bittersweet, and we won&#39;t be able to be together in the next life.  When we
phà kiếp sau hưa sẽ bên nhau bết được
hurt our bodies, it hurts too
kh bết thương xác thì đau rồi còn quá
quickly, so our feelings are hurt, what should we do? My
mau vậy tình cảm ta Cháo đau rồi làm sao
heart wants to say a
kh Trái Tim muốn nói một
word, I want to be with you for the rest of my
lời muốn bên em suốt cuộc
life, love each other in this
đời chót thương nhau ở kiếp
life, please don&#39;t make an appointment to go far
n xin đừng hẹn kếp đếp
away. The wound is so painful, it&#39;s still painful.  It&#39;s so
xa vết thương xắc th đau rồi còn quá
fast, our feelings are
mau vậy tình cảm ta
hurt, what should we do?
chao đau rồi làm sao
My heart wants to say a word, I want to be with you for
kh Trái Tim muốn nói một lời muốn bên em
the rest of my
suốt cuộc
life, love each other in this life,
đời chót thương nhau ở kiếp này
please don&#39;t let
xin đừng
go
kiếp
[music]
[âm nhạc]
Al
Al